Turner Memorial AME Church 2017.071 2017.071
Stage
- Women's Missionary, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Women Missionary Society, Wash Conf Branch Report to the Annual Conf, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- 47th Quadrennial Gen Conf, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- 47th Quadrennial Gen Conf, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Missionary Society, 2007 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- James for Bishop Committee and Missionary, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Night in Missions, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Johanna Morris Missionary Society, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Wash Conf Branch a Tribute, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Women Missionary Society, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Constitution and By Laws of WomenMissionary Society, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Constitution and By Laws of Johanna Morris, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Eighth Quadrennial Report of the Pension Department, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Quadrennial Report of Depat Finance, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Reportto Gen Conf by the President, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- "1969" (Box 51, Folder 20)
- Handy Little Book for the Missionary Sisters (Box 51, Folder 21)
- Tanner Turner Mem Service (Box 51, Folder 22)
- Sarah Allen (Box 51, Folder 23)
- Bernice Munson (Box 51, Folder 24)
- Missionary, 1951/2002 (Box 51, Folder 25)
- Missionary Society (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Loose Items (Box 51, Folder 27)
- Johanna Morris Missionary Society (Box 52, Folder 1)
- loose Items (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Bulletins (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Church Organizations, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Official Board Meeting, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Church Directory, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Missions on Missions and Welfare, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Turner's Church Directory, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Church Service Bulletin, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Membership Handbook (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Dr Martin Luther King Prayer Breakfast (Box 55, Folder 1)
- civil Rights (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Black History of AME Churches and Map (Box 55, Folder 3)
- African American History (Box 55, Folder 4)
- A Record of the Darker Race (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Bishops Roster, 1992/1996 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Bisshop Anderson, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Bishop George Barber (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Bishop Brookins, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Bishop Lawerence Hemingway (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Bishop Vashti Merphy McKenzie (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Bishop Pruitt, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Bishop Henry Turner (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Bishop Henry McNeal Turner (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Loose Items (Box 57, Folder 1)
- President Barack Obama, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Minutes of Official Board Meetings (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Frank Madison Reid Club, 1969/2002 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Reid Club Pink Tea (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Literary Club (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Gaines Club, 1951/1984 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- S E Guiles Club, 1969/1984 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Georgia Club (Box 60, Folder 6)
- I A Miller Circle (Box 60, Folder 7)
- I A Miller Club, 1969/1984 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Library and Historical Research (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Literary Club of Turner Presents (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Reid Club Celebrating, 1982/1984 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Pastor's Aid, 1969/1984 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Sons of Allen, 2007 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Senior Choir (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Stay Young (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Willing Workers Club, 1969/1984 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Young Peoples Department, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- organizations (Box 60, Folder 18)
- Gaines Club (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Varions Clubs (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Joshua Journal, 2010 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Rev Douglas, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Douglas for Bishop, 1991/1992 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Rev Douglas Photos (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Goodwin Douglas Circle (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Elder Douglas Photo (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Centennial ANNY, 2015 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- one hundredth anniversary, 2015 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Loose Items, 2015 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Isabelle Bond (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Cornell and Janice Brooks (Box 63, Folder 2)
- The Charles Coates (Box 63, Folder 3)
- The Clifton Cooper Family (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Doris Davis and Alice Wadsworth (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Edith Glenn (Box 63, Folder 6)
- The Robert Gregg Family (Box 63, Folder 7)
- The Joel Mcleod Family (Box 63, Folder 8)
- The Abraham McGill Family (Box 63, Folder 9)
- The Robert Newman Family (Box 63, Folder 10)
- The James Peterson Family (Box 63, Folder 11)
- the George Renrick, Jr. Family (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Paul and - Stanlly (Box 63, Folder 13)
- John Todd Sr. Family (Box 63, Folder 14)
- The Thomas Family Siblings (Box 63, Folder 15)
- The Marshall Williams Family (Box 63, Folder 16)
- The William Robinson Family (Box 63, Folder 17)
- The James Adams (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Ollie Lewis (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Bertha Mosbly Family (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Rev Douglas and Family (Box 63, Folder 21)
- The Neuby Family (Box 63, Folder 22)
- The Miller Family (Box 63, Folder 23)
- Vacation Bible School (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Vacation Bible School, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Vacation Bible School, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Vacation Bible School, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Capitol District Conference, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- 50th Anniversary Capitol District Conference, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- capitol District Conference, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Founders' Day, 2011 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Midyear Meeting, 2009 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Capitol District Conference, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- 2nd Episcopal District of Planning Meeting, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Washington Conference Choir, 2009 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Capital District Church School Convention, 2007 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- "2007" (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Capitol District Conference, 2007 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- 2nd Episcople, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Mid Year, 2005 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- "2002" (Box 65, Folder 14)
- "2000" (Box 65, Folder 15)
- "2000" (Box 65, Folder 16)
- "1998-1999" (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Philadelphia Annual Conference, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 18)
- District Conference of Capitol District, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- "1991" (Box 65, Folder 20)
- Mid Year Conference, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- Baltimore and Washington Annual Conference, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 22)
- Capitol District (Box 65, Folder 23)
- Christmas, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Season Greetings, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Prayer Breakfast (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Rev Edgar James, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Rev Edgar James (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Rev Edgar James (Box 67, Folder 3)
- James Rev Lipscomb (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Assorted Activities (Box 67, Folder 5)
- "1997" (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Rev James anf Turner Youths (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Rev Edgar James (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Rev James' Birthplace (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Photos od Rev James (Box 67, Folder 10)
- turner Welcomes (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Itinerant Deacon Certificate for Rev Edgar James, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Steward Board's Tribute to Rev James, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Rev James on the Nile River, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- James for Bishop, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 15)
- Rev James Funeral Service, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 16)
- Founder's Day Bulletin, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- AME Church, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- "1998", 1988 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Founder's Day, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Founder's Day, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- "1994" (Box 68, Folder 6)
- "1998" (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Founder's Day, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- "2007" (Box 68, Folder 9)
- "2010" (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Bible (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Bible (Box 69, Folder 2)